{
    "subject": "resource/The_Alphabet_Murders",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "The Alphabet Murders is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9363136291503906,
            "question": "Is 'The Alphabet Murders' a book or a movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7407099008560181,
            "question": "Can you think of other films that are similar to 'The Alphabet Murders'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.733022928237915,
            "question": "What kind of media is 'The Alphabet Murders'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6696842312812805,
            "question": "What is the main plot of 'The Alphabet Murders'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23009014129638672,
            "question": "Give an example of a film genre."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09098472446203232,
            "question": "What are some popular film genres?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08717945963144302,
            "question": "What makes a good film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06279869377613068,
            "question": "What are some elements commonly found in mystery films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04183180630207062,
            "question": "Who usually stars in mystery films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03620430454611778,
            "question": "Name a famous film director."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Alphabet Murders is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6916_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who usually stars in mystery films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6916_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some elements commonly found in mystery films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6916_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes a good film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6916_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6916_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6916_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6916_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6916_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6916_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6916_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6916_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6916_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6916_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6916_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the film \"The Alphabet Murders,\" confirming that it is indeed a type of film. This supports the statement that \"The Alphabet Murders\" is a film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}